<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Iridaceae</title><link>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on Iridaceae</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-pt</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 07:53:12 -0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ericakn.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Oct 2022 17:51:32 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/contact/</guid><description>E-mail: erica.k.nishimura@gmail.com
Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/%C3%A9rica-k-nishimura-2b1ab535/
Github: https://github.com/EricaKN</description></item><item><title>How to access a server using SSH-keys</title><link>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/posts/ssh/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 07:53:12 -0300</pubDate><guid>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/posts/ssh/</guid><description>Pre-requisites On this post, we are going to configure and access a server using SSH on:
Ubuntu 22.04 Linux machine Context During my first professional experience as a Data Scientist/ Engineer, I was responsible for a CNN (Convolutional Neural Network) model that predicts if the Electrocardiogram Exams (yes! It is that kind of heart-exam that children use to draw, with a continuous line!) presents a time-sensitive health condition, and if the patient needs to be prioritized for a doctor.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ericakn.github.io/blog/about/</guid><description>Name: Érica Kamimura Nishimura
Description:
&amp;ldquo;Seeker of Knowledge&amp;rdquo;. That is how I describe myself. Granddaughter of Japanese immigrants, I was born in Brazil, and since a very young age I have always been interested in learning new things. That is why I spent almost 2 years in Germany, exploring a new culture and learning a different approach to the studying process, the protection of the environment and social studies.
I graduated as an environmental engineer and, after starting to work with water treatment plants for municipalities in Brazil, I began a Master’s Degree in Sanitation and Hydraulic Engineering.</description></item></channel></rss>